and so when I got in the music business
I'm I'm A hip-hop head me too like to
the core I think a lot of people at this
point in my career don't really know
that about me
um well tell them Amanda
I mean what you want to do like do we
want to do do I need to wrap the entire
mob deep the infamous album like do I
need to do it but you want a freestyle
I mean I don't be nice I used to be nice
I do I always have two verses in my back
pocket I will say I mean um
that was me I spit in bars I didn't fuck
around drove a car imma stop here no
it's crazy because when you are a real
hip-hop head right and you come from
where we come from in that in the age of
we saw when rap came out and it's like
what is this what is that thing too oh
my God what is this what is that thing
to Global takeover this is it we run the
world so I saw that when I was
in Lee like I entered the music business
at that time like late uh sorry early
2000s is when shit yeah really took over
right that's when like hard knock life
went like diamonds and Eminem
and so that was a really like wild like
dope time to be a part of that and like
when I was on MTV I'm interviewing hoes
and Nas and hello everybody that I like
looked up to DMX many times
I interviewed DMX many times what's his
funeral Cry of course I was crushed by
that
um when I graduated from Colombia I got
my Master's at Columbia and the day I
came to work and they had gotten me a
cake and I had to interview X that day
and the cake was in the studio and he
came in the studio and was like what up
uh and I was like hello Mr X and then he
saw the cake and um even though the cake
did say congratulations Amanda
um but he thought the cake was for him
and so he put his hand in the cake and
eat it and I was like that was my cake
and he was like congratulations
um
and I was like all right but then now I
have that story yeah but you know X
all these folks like
for me like getting to be in that space
was like low-key like spiritual like it
was real and then at a certain time it
just stopped feeling like that um and I
knew that it was time to go yeah and so
that's when I pivoted and started like
looking for the next PATH and that's
when I found myself in comedy did you
lose any love for hip-hop with that one
thousand percent you know what it was
because the business started making me
hate the music because once I started
doing my own music and like trying to
navigate that space and having people
tell me like well you can't rap and sing
who does that you know which by the way
hilarious man yeah and and just like the
idea that like Talent didn't matter was
like Wow to me yeah like as a woman it
was just like that's irrelevant like
what's your story what are you willing
to you know give to this and I felt like
in order for me to be successful in
music the way that at the level I
consider to be success I would have had
to give up more of me than I was willing
to um and so then you know kind of just
like
I'm a really big believer like I I re I
uh I receive Omens
you know people say shit to me and I
hear it you know I filter it through I'm
not a stubborn person by any means and I
knew that it was time to come back to TV
because there was just a lot of people
just kind of that that just kept getting
sprinkled into my aura and I knew that I
wanted to do that
even though I was hosting and stuff I
just knew there was more for me but I'll
say all this to answer your question
TV then became at this point in my life
TV has become a space
that doesn't feel like a creative outlet
for me
it doesn't feel
it doesn't feel like a place where I can
be my full self and so that doesn't make
it doesn't feel valuable to me that's
why I like getting to do this radio show
like I get to be my full authentic self
you're doing this podcast you get to be
your full authentic self and I had to I
had to come to the realization that I
was kind of chasing these these like
benchmarks in TV that were for other
people and that were for shit that that
were for other people who don't care
about being there like like that's not
how do I say it some people don't even
have it they don't have it they just
it's not what they that's not their
their reason for doing this shit you
know what I mean like and so
um you know TV will find
its way
[Music]